<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="roles">
  <title>User Roles</title>
  <taskbody>
    <context>
      <p>
        A User Role defines the authorisation level or the operations a user can perform. Each User must have an
        associated Role.
      </p>

      <ol>
        <li>
          <b>User:</b> The default user-role. Is assigned on initial login to the CM portal, further User role authorisation must be assigned by request from CM portal Admin user.
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>Admin:</b> In addition to 'user' privileges, Admins can manage Users and perform all primary administrative tasks.
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>Super-Admin:</b> In addition to 'Admin' privileges, Super-Admins can perform CRUD
          operations on users and roles. This user-role has no restrictions.
        </li>
      </ol>
      <p>
        <b>NOTE:</b> This is only available to Admins and Super-Admins.
      </p>
      <p><b>Objective</b></p>
      <p>Create a new User Role within the CM Portal.</p>
      <p>
        <b>Outline</b>
        <ol>
          <li><xref href="#openRole">Open the Roles List-View</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#createRole">Create New User Role</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#enterDetails">Enter the User Role Details</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#saveRole">Save the User Role</xref></li>
        </ol>
      </p>
    </context>
    <steps>
      <step id="openRole">
        <cmd>Open the Roles List-View</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the Roles link in the navigation bar.</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="createRole">
        <cmd>Create New User Role</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the <b>Create new User Role</b> button.</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="enterDetails">
        <cmd>Enter the User Role Details</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Enter the details as shown below.</p>
          <p><b>NOTE:</b> Any restrictions on the fields are outlined.</p>
          <ul>
            <li><b>Name:</b> Name of the User Role.</li>
            <li><b>Permissions:</b> All the Paths that this user-role can access (e.g: /test) and the actions they are allowed to perform (e.g: get, put, post, delete).</li>

          </ul>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="saveRole">
        <cmd>Save User Role</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>
            Click the <b>Save</b> button, the User Role will be created, and the user will be
            redirected back to the view page for the newly created User Role.
          </p>
          <p>
            <b>NOTE:</b> User Role will not save if any fields are invalid (invalid fields
            are highlighted in red).
          </p>
        </info>
      </step>
    </steps>
    <result>
      <p>A New User Role is created in the CM Portal and can be assigned to users.</p>
    </result>
  </taskbody>
</task>
